desisexz.com 2008-06-26

# Desisexz | Desi Sex Videos | Free Indian Sex Videos | Indian Sex Stories Privacy Policy

### This is a privacy statement of Deisexz. This privacy statement describes how Desisexz collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: Desisexz.com.

For All Visitors to Our Sites:

Cookies: A "cookie" is a small text file that a Web site can place on your computer's hard drive in order, for example, to collect information about your activities on the site or to make it easier to use certain site functions. The cookie transmits this information back to the Web site's computer. Many users do not know that "cookies" are being placed on their computers when they visit Web sites. If you want to know when this happens, or prevent it from happening, you can set your browser to warn you when a Web site attempts to place a "cookie" on your computer.We use cookies to analyze how visitors, in the aggregate, use our Sites, in order to make our Sites as useful as possible for them. We do not use cookies to collect or store personally identifiable information.

Information automatically collected by our Sites:

Our servers automatically collect certain non-personally identifying information, such as your computer's IP address, the type of browser in use, and pages viewed, when you visit our Sites. We use this information to understand how visitors navigate through our Sites, to enhance your experience while using our Sites, and to make the materials we post as valuable to visitors as possible. We do not link this information to personally identifiable information.

Personal Information Sharing:

We will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties.We will share your personal information if we are required to do so by law.

Links to Other Web Sites:

Our Sites include links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of BlogsOnTop.com. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is subject to their privacy statements. Desisexz's privacy statement does not apply to information you may submit to those sites. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.
